forexabode.com 2014-06-22

# Privacy Policy and Copyrights - ForexAbode.com

## Privacy Policy and Copyrights- Overview:

ForexAbode.com hates spamming and shall not use any of your personal info for anything objectionable or any unwanted communication. Any contact information submitted on this site will be kept confidential and will be treated with utmost care.

It is prohibited to publish, reproduce or distribute, in any way, any of the content of the ForexAbode.com website whether in written, graphic or image, without our permission in writing.

### Privacy Policy – Details:

This privacy policy sets out how ForexAbode.com uses and protects any information that you submit to ForexAbode.com in order to register/subscribe.

ForexAbode.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

ForexAbode.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from October 1st, 2009.

#### What we collect

We may collect the following information:

**Mandatory:**  
• First Name and Last Name  
• Email Address  
• Country  
• Username (this is just a screen name and does not identify a real person or entity)

**Not mandatory:**  
• Phone number

What we do with the information we gather

What we require is mainly the email ID. The membership on this site is for the purpose of receiving emails for analysis updates of any other updates which we feel are important and can be useful to the members. And that’s what we do with the email address.

##### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. We have procedures in place to prevent any unauthorized access or disclosure. The information we receive from you is secure for any unauthorized use and spamming.

##### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over the other websites. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.  
Controlling your personal information

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission in writing or are required by law to do so. Though we do not engage ourselves in promoting other parties my the use of mailers but in some cases we may use your email ID to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting. You will have a control over it and in case any time you wish us to stop, we shall respect your decision.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

##### Contact Us

You may please use the contact form to contact us directly or write to us at contact(at)forexabode.com for any suggestions or complaints.
